(Sheldon:)Agh!
(Stuart:)Hey, uh, Leonard, things are a little tight
at the comic book store.
l might need some help
covering my share of the check.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah. No worries.
- And maybe a few bucks for the valet.
- Oh, all right.
- And gas money to get home.
- Yeah, sure.
(Stuart:)You know what,
this is my grandfather's watch...
(Sheldon:)- Oh.
- ...18-karat gold.
(Stuart:)- Got it in Europe during the war.
- Wow, it's very nice.
Mm-hm. A hundred bucks and it's yours.
(Raj:)Hey, everybody,
the bachelor boy has arrived.
(Sheldon:)ALL
For he's a jolly good fellow
(Raj:)For he's a jolly good fellow
(All(joining in):)Which nobody can deny
Yes, yes, yes, he's a jolly good fellow.
What time do the strippers arrive?
Actually, Barry, we're not gonna have
strippers tonight.
Ugh, then what the frig did I get
$200 in singles out for?